ANTONY BUDIANTO

SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER | OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTOR | WRITER

antonybudianto@gmail.com https://github.com/antonybudianto



PROFILE

Name: Antony Budianto DOB: August 8th, 1993 From: Pontianak, Indonesia

EDUCATION

Binus UniversityBachelor degree of Information
Systems major
2015

SKILLS

Technical skills

- HTML, CSS, JS, TypeScript
- React platform (Web, Native)
- Angular JS, Angular
- Jest, Webpack
- NodeJS, Golang
- Git, Jenkins + Travis CI, Docker

Soft skills

- Team-player, fast learner
- · Languages: English, Indonesia

SUMMARY

A senior software engineer and open source contributor with 4+ years experience on software development, web design and development, git, writing unit and end-to-end tests, deployment and setup CI server. Actively contributing to open source and listed as one of the top 10 JavaScript GitHub developer in Indonesia by git-awards.com

EXPERIENCE

Tokopedia | Senior Software Engineer

Jul 2018 - present

- Developing and maintaining front-end of Tokopedia Fintech products (Mitra Toppers, Personal Loan, Credit Card, Insurance, Mutual Funds, Gold, and more)
- Building CLI toolkit to standardize front-end tooling across current/ upcoming Tokopedia Fintech products which results in reusability, maintainability, and productivity

Tokopedia | Software Engineer

Sep 2017 - Jun 2018

GDP Labs | Sr. Software Development Engineer

Sep 2016 - Aug 2017

Developed HR platform web apps using Angular 2

GDP Labs | Software Development Engineer

Sep 2015 - Aug 2016

Developed vehicle insurance enterprise application using Angular JS

Binus University | Network Administrator

Sen 2014 - Aug 2015

 Cloning images for software lab computers, ensure networks running well, patching, calibration, maintenance, and develop various network-based applications

PROJECT

CRA Universal

https://github.com/antonybudianto/cra-universal

- Create React App companion CLI for universal app
- No eject, Zero config, Full HMR
- Supports server-side rendering with code-splitting

Gitfun

https://gitfun-web.herokuapp.com

- Simple GitHub client browser and repository summary
- Available on Web and Android (React Native)

Generated using https://github.com/antonybudianto/react-resume